## Anna Rusyayeva

Email: annarsve@gmail.com Mobile: +7(922)159-60-30

Github: https://github.com/VanillaWulf

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anna-rusyaeva-6b1276148

#### **SUMMARY**

Five years of experience in commercial development for varying business areas provided me with the skill to understand client's goals and to create tasks to achieve it. Thanks to a solid set of marketing tools, I promote the relevant customers in the right direction according to the needed intention. Moreover, with the help of excellent building communications with current teams and contractors, I clearly plan tasks and hand over projects on time.

#### **SKILLS**

- **Agile** (SCRUM, Kanban, scrumban)
- **Managing projects** (Trello, Jira)
- E-commerce (Yandex Direct, Yandex Metrics, Google AdWords, Google Analytics)
- Market research
- Marketing (POSM, presentations, mailings)
- Sales analytics
- User demand analysis
- Developing cases for new products/features (IDEF, UML)
- **Design** (sketch, mogups, figma, adobe products)
- Strong technical stack (HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, Angular, git)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelancer September 2018 Mobile app development

- Websites development
- Payment system development

#### Senior Marketing Manager - 000 'Ideco'

October 2017 - June 2018

- Project management (launch, maintaining and updating)
- Development process management (technical specifications for designers and developers)
- Organisation Agile workflow (Jira, Trello)
- Planning budgets
- Creating roadmaps
- **SMM**
- **POSM**
- Sales analytics
- Making bases for cold calling
- Quarterly reports about efficiency of marketing activities

#### **SEO Specialist** - Advertising Agency 'Index Art'

January 2017 - October 2017

- Technical auditing (layout, structure, accessibility)
- Task management Technical auditing (developers, designers, writers)
- Creation and testing of hypotheses for increasing traffic (ui/ux, structure, HTML, core, content)



**PROJECTS** 



Development + marketing strategy

#### **Landing Page**



Development + marketing strategy

#### **Catalog of projects**



Web catalog development based on printed one

#### **Domain relocation**



Domain relocation without organic traffic loses

**Website** 

- Attendance and behavior analytics
- Creating monthly reports for customers

# НОЧЛЕЖКА

Design + development.

**Emailing** 

### **Context Advertising and SEO Specialist -**

Advertising Agency 'ManyLetters'

- Creating and running campaigns in Yandex. Direct, Google AdWords, MyTarget
- Coordination updates with clients
- Writing specifications for programmers
- Creating monthly reports for customers

#### **Software Engineer -**

October 2013 - September 2014

December 2015 - September 2016

Special design bureau 'Peleng'

- Writing technical specification for software
- Detecting of software functionality flaws
- Revising software in C++
- Modular and integration testing

February 2015

## company.



Newsletter for the

App for iOS & Android

#### **EDUCATION**

Beijing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics Master of Computer Science

**Ural Federal University** 2015

Master of Computer Science in Technology in Mathematical Software and Information Systems Administration

**Ural Federal University** 2013

Higher Professional Education in Legal Regulation of Business

**Ural Federal University** 2013

Bachelor of Computer Science in Technology in Design and Technology of Electronic Means

#### **Payment system**



App for shools

#### **LANGUAGES**

Russian native speaker English - B2